goldieblox.com 2017-03-26

# Privacy Policy – GoldieBlox

## GOLDIEBLOX PRIVACY POLICY

Scope:

This Privacy Policy applies to customer personal information collected by GoldieBlox, Inc., a Delaware corporation, through our family of websites, including [www.goldieblox.com](http://www.goldieblox.com/) and www.bloxtown.com.

GoldieBlox recognizes the importance of our customers' privacy. This Policy describes:

  * How and why we collect your personal information.
  * How your information is used and protected.
  * When and with whom we share your information.
  * The choices you can make about how we collect, use, and share your information.

****Information We Collect****

We collect personal information about you to deliver the products and services you request and to help improve your shopping experience. We strive to limit the amount of personal information collected to support the intended purpose of the collection.

****Information You Give Us****

We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways when you interact with GoldieBlox through our websites. Some examples are when you:

  * Create an account on one of our websites;
  * Make an online purchase from us;
  * Request customer service or contact us;
  * Submit a GoldieBlox related story, testimonial, rating or review, or other user-generated content that may be posted on the site;
  * Participate in a contest, sweepstake, promotion, or survey; or
  * Otherwise submit personal information to us along with any related content of the communication.

Personal information is information that identifies you or is reasonably linked to you. The personal information we collect may include contact and payment information like your name, email and physical addresses, phone numbers, and credit and debit card information. When you ask us to ship an order, we may collect information you provide us such as the name, address, and phone number of recipients. For certain transactions, we may be required to collect information to comply with legal requirements.

****Information from Other Sources****

****Automated Information Collection****

We receive and store certain types of information when you interact with our websites, emails, and online advertising. Our purpose is to allow the websites to work correctly, to evaluate use of the website, and to support website analytics and marketing campaigns. Some examples include:

We may collect technical information such as your internet protocol address, your device operating system and browser type, the address of a referring website, if any, and the path you take through our websites.

We use "cookies" to recognize you as you use or return to our sites. This is done so that we can provide a continuous and more personalized shopping experience for you. A cookie is a small text file that a website or email may save to your browser and store on your hard drive.

We may also use web beacons. Beacons allow us to know if a certain page was visited, an email was opened, or if ad banners on our website and other sites were effective.

Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our Users, we are not able to respond to Do Not Track signals from your browser at this time, as we believe that there is no consistent industry standard for how to respond to Do Not Track browser settings.

****How We Use Your Information****

GoldieBlox uses your information to offer and provide our products and services and to support our core business functions. These include order or service fulfillment, internal business processes, marketing, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. Some examples include:

  * To fulfill your requests for products and services and communicate with you about those requests;
  * To register and service your account;
  * To administer surveys, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions;
  * To provide customer service and alert you to product information, including recalls;
  * To help us improve and customize our service offerings, websites, and advertising;
  * To send you information about our products, services, and promotions; and
  * To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business.

To accomplish these purposes, we may combine personal and non-personal information we collect with offline information, including information from third parties. We may transfer or disclose your information within our corporate family of companies for these purposes.

****How We Disclose Your Information Outside GoldieBlox****

GoldieBlox does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We only disclose your personal information with your prior consent or under the following limited circumstances.

****Service Providers****

We may disclose or otherwise make available personal information about you to service providers that help with our business operations. Examples are shipping vendors, billing and refund vendors, payment card processors, and companies that help us improve our product and service offerings and our websites. Your personal information may be stored and processed by our service providers in the United States or other locations where the service providers or GoldieBlox maintain facilities. We require our service providers to keep your information secure. In addition, our service providers may not use or disclose personal information for any purpose other than providing the services on our behalf.

****Legal Requirements and Protection of Our Company and Others****

We may disclose your information in other special circumstances. These include situations when the sharing is necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of GoldieBlox, our customers, our associates, or any other person, or where otherwise required by law. GoldieBlox may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

****Marketing Purposes****

From time to time with your consent, we may disclose information with carefully selected companies who may offer you products and services of interest. You may opt in to this sharing under the "Your Choices" section below.

****Business Transfers****

We may transfer any information we have about you in connection with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of GoldieBlox or as part of a corporate reorganization, merger, or stock sale or other change in corporate control.

****Data Collection, Use, or Disclosure****

GoldieBlox collects, uses, or discloses your personal information consistent with this policy. The method of obtaining consent is appropriate for the type of personal information being collected, used, or disclosed. For example, we will obtain your express consent (verbal, written, or electronic agreement) to collect, use, or disclose personal information in accordance with law. In other situations, we consider consent to be implied, such as to use your email for marketing purposes, unless you opt out of these communications such as by unsubscribing.

****Marketing Preferences****

We want to communicate with you in ways you want to hear from us. Examples are newsletters, special offers, and new product announcements. We use the following standards for marketing communications:

We use an opt-in standard for phone and text messages. We also use an opt-in standard for sharing personal information with third parties for marketing purposes. Opt-in means we will only conduct the activity with your express consent.

We use an opt-out standard for email or for other communications like mail. Opt-out means we consider your consent is implied, but will stop the activity on your request.

If you contact us by email or mail, please be sure to include your full name, the types of communications you would like to receive or not receive, and your related contact information. For instance, if you would like to opt-out of mail, include your mailing address. Please allow sufficient time for your preferences to be processed. It may take up to 10 days to process your requests related to email and 4-6 weeks for other requests.

Please be aware that, even if you have opted out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still contact you for transactional purposes. Some examples are contacts for customer service, product information, service or reminder notices, or recalls. We may also need to contact you with questions or information regarding your order, such as regarding order status, shipment, or refunds.

****Third Party Tracking and Online Advertising****

We may permit third party ad networks, social media companies, and other third party services to collect information about browsing behavior from visitors to our websites through cookies, social plug-ins, or other tracking technology. We may permit third party online advertising networks to collect information about your use of our websites over time so that they may play or display ads that may be relevant to your interests on our Service as well as on other websites or services. Typically, the information is collected through cookies or similar tracking technologies. The only way to completely “opt out” of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies and how you may opt-out of some of this tracking, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)). Depending on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through settings. If you have any questions about opting out of the collection of cookies and other tracking/recording tools, you can contact us directly at [service@goldieblox.com](mailto:service@goldieblox.com).

****How to Access and Update Your Information****

GoldieBlox takes reasonable steps to keep your personal information accurate and complete. You can access or update your personal information, including contact or account information, in the following ways:

If you have created an account on our website, log into your account. Once you do, you will be able to enter and update your own contact information and payment information, as well as contact information for recipients you have designated.

If you need help accessing your information related to a service provided by a third party, we will assist you by referring you to the third party. Please contact us via the "Contact Us" section below.

****How We Secure Your Information****

Securing your information is a company priority. Whether you are shopping on our websites or in our stores, we use reasonable security measures to help protect the confidentiality of personal information.

****Online Protections****

Your account information is protected by the password you use to access your online account. Please keep this password confidential.

##### ****Privacy of Children Online****

We are committed to protecting children's online privacy. Our websites are for a general audience and are not geared towards children. In order to protect the privacy of children, GoldieBlox websites and mobile applications do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent. Please contact us via the "Contact Us" section of this Policy if you believe we may have collected information from your child and we will work to delete it.

##### ****Goldie's Birthday Club Terms and Conditions****

  1. You may enroll a child in Goldie’s Birthday Club at http://www.goldieblox.com/pages/birthday-club. To enroll a child (each such child the “Recipient”), you must be at least 18 years old and must provide your valid email address, Recipient’s name, Recipient’s date of birth, and Recipient’s mailing address. By providing your information to GoldieBlox you agree that such information may be added to our customer file and may be used to, among other things, contact you with information about our products, offers, special promotions and upcoming events that may interest you.  GoldieBlox will not use the Recipient’s information for any other purpose other than to administer Goldie’s Birthday Club.  Recipient’s participation in Goldie’s Birthday Club and our use of your information shall at all times be subject to these Terms and Conditions.  If you have any questions regarding these policies or the manner in which we use your information, please contact us at [service@goldieblox.com](mailto:service@goldieblox.com).

  2. Goldie’s Birthday Club is available to Recipients with physical mailing addresses residing within the U.S. or Canada. GoldieBlox reserves the right to limit the number of Recipients per household.

  3. You are responsible for keeping Recipient’s information up to date. You may update Recipient’s address or cancel Recipient’s enrollment in Goldie’s Birthday Club at any time by reaching out to our customer service team at [service@goldieblox.com](mailto:service@goldieblox.com).

  4. We may modify these Terms and Conditions at any time by posting such modifications on our website. If you object to a modification, your sole recourse will be to terminate Recipient’s enrollment and request the removal of your information from our database by emailing us at [service@goldieblox.com](mailto:service@goldieblox.com). We also reserve the right to discontinue the Goldie’s Birthday Club at any time without notice.

****Changes to the GoldieBlox Privacy Policy****

Please check our privacy Policy periodically for changes. We will also notify you of significant updates and will post the date it was last updated at the bottom of the privacy Policy.

****Contact Us****

Email GoldieBlox customer service at: service@goldieblox.com.

Mail:

GoldieBlox , Inc.

2230 Livingston Street

Oakland, CA 94606

****Your California Privacy Rights****

Our privacy Policy describes how we share information for marketing purposes. The Policy and rights apply to all customers, including California residents:

We share information with others outside of GoldieBlox only if we have your express consent (opt-in).

Please contact us with any questions, or to request a list of third parties to whom we may disclose information for marketing purposes and the categories of information we may disclose, via the Contact Us section above.

****DMCA Notice****

Procedure for Making and Responding to Claims of Copyright Infringement

It is the policy of GoldieBlox to respond to claims of copyright infringement. We will promptly process and investigate notices of alleged infringement by third parties and will take appropriate actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, Title 17, United States Code, Section 512(c)(2) (the "DMCA"), where applicable.

Pursuant to the DMCA, notifications of claimed copyright infringement by third parties should be sent to our Designated Agent. If you believe that your copyrighted work has been infringed under U.S. copyright law and is accessible on this Web Site, please notify us by contacting our Designated Agent. Even if you believe that the alleged infringing work was not posted by a third party, please send all notifications of claimed copyright infringement to our Designated Agent listed below.

To be effective under the DMCA, notification of claims of copyright infringement by third parties must be a written communication to our Designated Agent that includes the following:

A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;

Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material; single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;

Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit Walmart.com to locate the material;

Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted;

A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and

A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Our Designated Agent for notice of claims of copyright infringement can be reached as follows:

By mail:

GoldieBlox, Inc.

2230 Livingston Street

Oakland, CA 94606

By e-mail:

[service@goldieblox.com]

This contact information is only for reporting claims of copyright infringement. Contact information for other matters is provided elsewhere on this Web Site.

Upon receipt of a valid notification of alleged copyright infringement by a third party, we will remove or disable access to the material identified in the notice, forward the written notification to the alleged infringer, and take reasonable efforts to notify the alleged infringer that it has removed or disabled access to this material.

You should be aware that, under the DMCA, claimants who make misrepresentations concerning copyright infringement may be liable for any damages, including costs and attorneys' fees, incurred by the alleged infringer or by GoldieBlox, if injured by relying upon such misrepresentation in removing or disabling access to the material or activity claimed to be infringing.

If a notice of copyright infringement has been filed against you, you may file a counter notification with the Designated Agent at the address listed above.

To be effective, a counter notification must be a written communication provided to the our Designated Agent that includes the following:

A physical or electronic signature;

Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or access to it was disabled;

A statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled; and

Your name, address, and telephone number, and a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of Federal District Court for the judicial district in which the address is located and that you will accept service of process from the complainant who provided the original notification or an agent of such person or entity.

If we receive a valid counter notification, we shall provide the complainant with a copy of the counter notification, inform the complainant that it will replace the removed material or cease disabling access to it in 10 to 14 days from receipt of the counter notification, and replace the removed material or cease disabling access to it in 10 to 14 business days, provided that we have not received notice from the complainant that an action has been filed seeking a court order to restrain the alleged infringer from engaging in infringing activity relating to the material on our system.

You should be aware that the DMCA provides substantial penalties for a false counter notice filed in response to a notice of copyright infringement. Claimants who make misrepresentations in their the counter notification statement may be liable for any damages, including costs and attorneys' fees, incurred by any copyright owner or copyright owner's authorized licensee, or by us, if injured by relying upon such misrepresentation in replacing the removed material or ceasing to disable access to it.

Last Updated: September 15th, 2014.
